opentracker.net 2014-06-26

# privacy statement | Opentracker - Digital Analytics

### your privacy

Most importantly: we will not sell, trade, give, etc., the statistics that we collect on your site to any third party, without your express permission. The data that we collect is not mined or used for marketing purposes in any way. The data that we collect is used solely for purposes of web metrics and traffic analysis by Opentracker.net. Be assured that safeguarding the contents of your website traffic is our priority.

Opentracker.net, is committed to safeguarding your privacy on-line. The following statement sets our privacy policy. For the purposes of this privacy statement "Opentracker.net" shall mean Opentracker.net. This policy may change from time to time so please re-read this policy periodically.

### what we gather from you

Our site collects information in several ways. When you order information, registrations and services from us you are required to complete a client order form. Opentracker.net requests your name, e-mail address, financial information (such as payment details and credit card details) and your contact information ("Customer Information").

As part of our service, Opentracker.net also uses cookies to help identify you and access your account data, to track you, to track traffic patterns and for system administration. A cookie is a small text file that is created by your browser from a web page and is stored on your computer's hard drive.

### contact information

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information is used to get in touch with them when necessary. Financial information collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

### third party intermediaries

Opentracker.net verifies the credit card information given by you through a 3rd party clearing companies "PayPal", "Worldpay" or "Chargify". This clearing company is solely a link in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or in any other way use the information they obtain from us.

### parties to whom we disclose your information

The data that we collect on your site will not be transmitted to a 3rd party without your express permission. Meaning, that we will not, and do not, mine your data for marketing purposes, nor disclose the details of your traffic to a third party, without your express permission.

Opentracker.net may disclose Customer Information in special cases where Opentracker.net has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our terms and conditions of use or may be causing injury or interference with our rights, property, our customers or anyone who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose Customer Information when we believe, in good faith, that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes necessary to maintain services and improve our products and services.

You should also note that the servers hosting our systems are located in a number of different countries including The Netherlands and the United States. This means that the information you provide will be transferred to and hosted on servers in these countries and by submitting the requested information you hereby expressly consent to such transfers.

### security

This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. A password must be entered to log in to your account and in order to manage your domain name(s). All personal information is fully encrypted during all transactions. Please note, however, that no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure. As a result, while we endeavour to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us and you transmit such information to us at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission we endeavour to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems. Please note that Opentracker.net will never ask for any personal information via email (e.g. marriage status, income, etc.).

### correct/update

If you wish to correct, update or otherwise modify the information that you have provided to us please visit the Profile section on our web site and correct, update or modify the relevant information.

### contacting the web site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web site, please e-mail [privacy@opentracker.net](mailto:privacy@Opentracker.net)

### links

This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are 'clicking' to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.
